HELLO EVERYONE,THIS IS RUPAM KUMARI AND I'M MAKING THIS VIDEO TO GIVE YOU THE DETAILS OF MY CURRENT TASK AT EY. Basically, MY PROJECT IS RELATED TO THE CLIMATE CHANGE AND SUSTAINABILITY AND I PERSONALLY THINK THAT IT IS ONE OF THE MOST CRITICAL AND RELEVANT TOPICS THAT EVERYONE NEED TO CONSIDER FROM THEIR SIDE. One need to know that THERE ARE THREE CATEGORIES that ONE NEED TO BE AWARE OF , THAT IS E(ENVIRONMENTAL), S(SOCIAL) AND G (GOVERNANCE) CONSTITUTING TO TERM ESG, is a framework used by investors and stakeholders to assess a company's non-financial performance and long-term sustainability, through covering its impact on the planet, people, and how it's run. It goes beyond traditional financial metrics to gauge a company's commitment to responsible practices, influencing investment decisions, risk management, and overall reputation, and is central to sustainable investing. In addition to this, There are also several steps taken by countries on sustainability, one of that is Paris agreement, that one should go through.So, this was for everyone's knowledge.HOWEVER, MY CURRENT RESEARCH IS ON GREEN HYDROGEN AND ITS IMPACT IN REAL WORLD.let's start with hydrogen, as we know Hydrogen is already in use in industrial applications — either as-it-is or through a conversion into ammonia. Therefore, there is already a value chain in place based on production , virtual pipeline and storage close to industrial plants.However Hydrogen comes in three form of colors that is gray, blue and green that has different implications to understand.Related to the research I'm currently exploring the topic of Green hydrogen, So Hydrogen is defined as green if it is generated from water and renewable energy to power the electrolyzers, making the process completely green and sustainable.However, the need for greener generation, expected growth in traded volumes, and new and increasing applications will require an evolution in the sector’s current configuration, bringing several opportunities for investment across the value chain, including:1. New technologies for hydrogen production2. secondly, New business models and solutions for transportation and distribution3. others include, New applications as a green energy sourceIf above achieved, then green hydrogen can help to decarbonize a variety of sectors and create numerous business opportunities across the value chain, from power generation and transportation to energy and industrial feedstock.Now let's come to the point, that is the client's objective.so According to the asked question or target set by client:The client has set the target to Reduce scope 1, 2 and 3 GHG emissions by 45% per short ton of goods delivered by 2030 (from a 2015 base year).So, how to solve this using green hydrogen, given client has already started to transition parts of their short-haul fleet to EVso for this, Green hydrogen implementation can help reduce Scope 1, 2, and 3 greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions by directly replacing fossil fuels, decarbonizing electricity sources, and cleaning up supply chain activities in hard-to-abate sectors.with this,let's move ahead with advantages of using green hydrogen in production keeping in mind the client's goal. some of them are:1. it drastically cut emissions2. it can be produced anywhere from a variety of resources3. third, it can be stored in trucks4. fourth, In cases where hydrogen is already used as an input to the process, conversion into green hydrogen requires less investment and the cost gap is smaller, allowing it to reach cost competitiveness sooner.5.  others include boosting energy security, and enabling large-scale renewable energy storage creating significant economic opportunities : 1. like in decarbonizing heavy industries (for example steel, chemicals, transport) 2. second, in power grids through its versatility as a fuel 3. also in feedstock, and grid stabilizerso above covers the benefits and opportunities of green hydrogen.Now let's come to the challenges/ barriers that our client might face in implementation: 1. first, lack of financial or regulatory incentives2. second, insufficient access to hydrogen3. third, related to shippers (our client’s clients) those prioritizing cost-effectiveness and speed rather than emissions reduction, etc.4. fourth, lack of demand for decarbonization5. last but not least, the level of “green” depends on the fuels used in hydrogen productionso this covers the advantages and disadvantages of green hydrogen. Now there are numerous ways organizations are currently into this area:1.first category: Organizations that are currently using gray hydrogen are particularly well-poised to take advantage of the green hydrogen wave as first movers. 2. second category: Organizations that can benefit from a green hydrogen revolution are developing strategies and testing business models. 3. third category: Even organizations that have no hydrogen agenda but want to reduce their carbon footprint can be thinking about green hydrogen now.and can be other categories too.So this sums up my research on the topic of "Green Hydrogen". so, Thank you for your time and i hope everyone can consider climate and sustainability in more serious way than before.